# OLATUNJI AYOBAMI

### Frontend Developer (React.JS)

#### **SUMMARY**

A FrontEnd developer with 3 years+ development and production experience with HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS and the technology built around it like React, Webpack, Enzyme, Redux, and Flux. I also have successfully used these technologies in building some real-world projects which can be found in my GitHub repositories and my portfolio. I love to convert designs into quality and well optimized code. I also like to collaborate with others to solve problems and work together as a team.

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Address:

No 19B Anuoluwapo Street, Mushin, Lagos, Nigeria.

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

(+234)7017521808

🖾 olatunjiayobami575@gmail.com

Github: haywhyvilla

iii Linkedln: Olatunji-Ayobami

O Twitter: Olatunji-Ayobami

FEB 2021 - AUG 2021

# **Work Experience**

#### React JS Developer(contract)

BRIDAM Inc. DEC 2022 - PRESENT

- + interpretation of Designs created by the Ui UX Designer
- + Consumption and implementation of APis created by the Backend Developer
- + Development and Management of Multiple Dynamic Web Apps
- + implementation of Git Version Control System

#### **Frontend Developer**

FAMESIFY Team, Inc. APR 2022 - DEC 2022

- + integrate platforms together via third party tools, APis and Webhooks
- + Development and Management of Multiple Dynamic Web Apps
- + Partnered with my team members to assign tasks and follow set guidelines.
- + Responsible for the entire web software mobile responsiveness

#### Frontend Developer(Intern)

ZURI Team, Inc. AUG 2021 - APR 2022

- + Design Landing Pages and Funnels on various CMS and CRMs
- + Integrate platforms together via third party tools, APIs and Webhooks
- + Partnered with my team members to assign tasks and follow set guidelines.
- + Migrate setup from existing platform to another

#### Freelance FrontEnd Developer

# UPWORK FREELANCE

+ Design responsive and professional e-commerce, real estate, mortgage, etc websites

- + Optimize website loading speed and fix errors on the website.
- + Redesign existing website to improve UI and increase conversion.

## Education

#### (B. Sc.) Material Engineering

UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN 2015 - 2021

# **Skills**

HTML5 CSS JavaScript SASS Tailwind Bootstrap ReactJS Redux Git Github Figma

## **Certificates**

**ZURI Training**  $\bigcirc$